(Leonard:)...and the longest conversation you've had
with a woman was when your mom called.
Wow, you're just gonna make me
come out and say it, aren't you?
(Leonard:)Say what?
(Howard:)You're weighing me down.
(Howard:)I'm a falcon who hunts better solo.
(Leonard:)Fine, I'll sit here.
You take flight and hunt.
(Howard:)Don't be ridiculous.
You can't just tell a falcon when to hunt.
(Leonard:)Actually, you can.
(Leonard:)There's a whole sport built around it.
(Leonard:)Falconry.
(Howard:)Shut up.
(Howard:)Let's just get Koothrappali and go.
(Howard:)Lucky bastard.
It's gotta be that stupid accent of his.
[IN INDIAN ACCENT]
Hello, I'm Sanjay Wolowitz from Bombay.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Okay, I'm stumped.